thekoalition.com 2010-05-25

# Privacy Policy | The Koalition

## [Privacy Policy](http://www.thekoalition.com/privacy-policy/ "Permanent Link to Privacy Policy")

**Collection and Use of Information:** In addition to any personally identifying information you may voluntarily provide during your visit to this website, The Koalition may recognize and record certain other information, including without limitation, your computer’s unique IP address, and/or any other information concerning your use of this website. The Koalition reserves the right to use any information it collects at this website for any legal purpose, including without limitation by sending you information concerning future products, activities and/or promotions, and/or by sharing your information with third-parties in connection with certain promotions, products, programs and/or services. You may contact us by email at **Legal@thekoalition.com**

**Cookies:** Cookies are small text files that contain a string of alphanumeric characters. The Koalition reserves the right to use “cookies” at this website, by which one computer transaction may be related with a later one. By way of example, cookies may be used to save passwords or preferences or otherwise keep track of website access. For more information about cookies please visit: [www.allaboutcookies.org/cookies/](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/cookies/)

**Children:** No visitor to this website under 18 years of age may submit and/or post any information to this website without the consent of a parent or guardian. Notwithstanding the foregoing, The Koalition does not seek to collect any personally identifiable information of children under 13 years of age and no such information should be submitted and/or posted to this website.

**Policy Changes:** The Koalition reserves the right to change this policy, in whole or part, at any time in its sole and absolute discretion, without prior notice, effective upon providing the updated policy on this website. If you have any questions concerning this policy, please submit your written questions to **legal@thekoalition.com**

For policies concerning our merchandise please visit [Spreadshirts policy page](http://www.spreadshirt.com/us/US/-/Privacy-3259/).
